{
    "subject": "resource/WVAH-TV",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Charleston,_West_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "WVAH-TV is located in Charleston, West Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9544013142585754,
            "question": "Where is WVAH-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.892615795135498,
            "question": "What state is WVAH-TV in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8559557795524597,
            "question": "In what city can you find WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8329805135726929,
            "question": "Where are WVAH-TV's studios situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8130671381950378,
            "question": "In which US state would you find WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7958399057388306,
            "question": "Is WVAH-TV a television station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7776615023612976,
            "question": "What city is the home of WVAH-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721664905548096,
            "question": "To which state does WVAH-TV belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.766302227973938,
            "question": "What is the location of WVAH-TV's broadcasting operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.764529287815094,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where WVAH-TV broadcasts from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WVAH-TV is located in Charleston, West Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_417_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of WVAH-TV's broadcasting operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_417_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which state does WVAH-TV belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_417_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is the home of WVAH-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_417_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_417_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about WVAH-TV's location and licensing details, which supports the statement that \"WVAH-TV is located in Charleston, West Virginia.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}